This is a wood saw, but what would happen if, by accident, you touched it?
Well, most wood saws have a protective device to save your finger or hand,
and it's really impressive how it works.
The saw blade transmits a small electrical signal.
When the skin comes into contact with the blade, the signal changes because the human body is a driver.
The signal change activates the security system, which activates the brake.
At this moment, a high aluminum brake, the spinning stick, stops it in less than 5 milliseconds.
Then, the blade pushes under the table, eliminating the risk of subsequent contact,
and the engine is cut off.
And in the process, saving your finger.